Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Falla, Manuel de (Box-folder 30/27)
  - Farmer, Dr. Frank C. (Box-folder 30/28)
  - Farnam, Lynwood (Box-folder 30/29)
  - Farrand, Beatrix (Box-folder 30/30)
  - Farrand, Max see Huntington (Henry E.) Library and Art Gallery
  - Farrar, Geraldine (fund appeal) (Box-folder 30/31)
  - Farrell, James T. (fund appeal) (Box-folder 30/32)
  - Farrington, Isobelle Scudder (Box-folder 30/33)
  - Farwell, Arthur (Box-folder 30/34)
  - Fass, Marjorie (Box-folder 30/35)
  - Fassett, James H. see Columbia Broadcasting System. Fassett, James H.
  - Fay, Charles Norman and Mrs. (Box-folder 30/36)
  - Fay, William Rodman (Box-folder 30/37)
  - "Fe" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Feakins, William B. (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Fearon, Walter (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Fedorovsky, Paul see also Averino, Olga (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Fekete Zoltan (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Felber, Hermann (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Feldman, Samuel (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Felici, Alicita (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Fellowes, Edmund Horace (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Felman, Hazel (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Felton, Cora Smedberg (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Fenn, H. A. (lawyer) (Box-folder 31/12)
  - Fergus, Phyllis (Box-folder 31/13)
  - Férir, Emile (Box-folder 31/14)
  - Ferner, Walter V. (Box-folder 31/15)
  - Ferrier, André (Box-folder 31/16)
  - Ferry, Abby F. (Box-folder 31/17)
  - Ferry, Ann H. (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Fessenden, Hart see also Farrell, James T. (Box-folder 31/19)
  - Fetter, Helen (Box-folder 31/20)
  - Feustmann, M. M. see Scopes & Feustmann
  - Feytmanns, Gustave (Box-folder 31/21)
  - "Fi" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 31/22)
  - Fiakova, Elizabetha (Box-folder 31/23)
  - Ficher, Jacobo (Box-folder 31/24)
  - Fiedler, Arthur (Box-folder 31/25)
  - Fiedler, Samuel (Box-folder 31/26)
  - Field Museum of Natural History see Chicago. Field Museum of Natural History
  - Fierlinger, Jos. (Box-folder 31/27)
  - Filene, Lincoln (Box-folder 31/28)
  - Fine, Irving (Box-folder 31/29)
  - Fine Arts Quartet (Box-folder 31/30)
  - Finney, Ross Lee (Box-folder 31/31)
  - Firestone, Nathan and Hilda (Box-folder 31/32)
  - "Fis" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 31/33)
  - Fischer, Carl (firm) see also Reese, Gustave (Box-folder 31/34)
  - Fisher, (first name unknown) (Box-folder 31/35)
  - Fisher, Dorothy Canfield (Box-folder 31/36)
  - Fisher, Herbert Albert L. (Box-folder 31/37)
  - Fisher, Mabel (Box-folder 31/38)
  - Fisher, Margaret, 1934-1952 (Box-folder 31/39)
  - Fisher, Margaret, 1953 and undated (Box-folder 31/40)
  - Fisher, Ruth Page see Page, Ruth
  - Fisher, Thomas Hart see Page, Ruth
  - Fisher, William Arms, Mrs. (Box-folder 31/41)
  - Fisk University (Box-folder 31/42)
  - Fitelberg, Jerzy (Box-folder 31/43)
  - "Fl" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 31/44)
  - Flagg, Marion (Box-folder 31/45)
  - Flagler, Harry Harkness (Box-folder 31/46)
  - Flammand, J.C.J. see France. Legion of Honor
  - Flanders, Helen Hartness (Box-folder 31/47)
  - Flaschner, O., & co. (Box-folder 31/48)
  - Fleck, Henry T. (Box-folder 31/49)
  - Fleischer, Antal (Box-folder 31/50)
  - Flesch, Carl (Box-folder 31/51)
  - Fletcher, Maisie (Box-folder 31/52)
  - Fletcher, Victor S. (Box-folder 31/53)
  - Fleury, Louis, 1923-1925 (Box-folder 31/54)
  - Fleury, Louis and Gabrielle, 1926-circa 1938 (Box-folder 31/55)
  - Flonzaley Quartet (Box-folder 31/56)
  - Florence Nightingale Institute of Honorables (Box-folder 31/57)
  - "Fo" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Foertner, Hilda E. (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Fogg Art Museum see Harvard University. Fogg Art Museum
  - Folger, Henry C., Mrs. (Emily C.J. Folger) (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library see also Folger, Henry C., Mrs. (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Fonaroff, Vera, 1917-1929 (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Fonaroff, Vera, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Fonaroff, Vera, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Fonaroff, Vera, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 32/8)
  - Fonaroff, Vera, undated (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Fontaine, Lilian (Box-folder 32/10)
  - Fontenoy, Viscontesse de (Box-folder 32/11)
  - Fooshé, Ruth J. (Box-folder 32/12)
  - Foot, N. Chandler, Mrs. (Box-folder 32/13)
  - Foote, Arthur (Box-folder 32/14)
  - Forbes, Edward W. and Margaret see also Harvard University. Fogg Art Museum (Box-folder 32/15)
  - Ford Hall Forum see Boston, Mass. Ford Hall Forum
  - Forsyth, Cecil (Box-folder 32/16)
  - Fortnightly Club see Chicago. Fortnightly Club
  - Foss, Lukas (Box-folder 32/17)
  - Foulds, John (Box-folder 32/18)
  - Fowles, Helen M. (Box-folder 32/19)
  - Fox, Félix (Box-folder 32/20)
  - Fox, Susan E. (Box-folder 32/21)
  - Fox, Virgil (Box-folder 32/22)
  - Fox-Strangways, A. H. (Box-folder 32/23)
  - Fox Piano Company (Box-folder 32/24)
  - "Fr" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 32/25)
  - Fraenkel, Wolfgang (Box-folder 32/26)
  - France (Box-folder 32/27)
  - France. Legion of Honor see also American Society of the French Legion of Honor (Box-folder 32/28)
  - Francis, Elaina Thayer (Box-folder 32/29)
  - Francis, Henry and Agnes (Box-folder 32/30)
  - Franck, César, Memorial Committee (Box-folder 32/31)
  - Franco, Johan (Box-folder 32/32)
  - Franco-American Music Society (Box-folder 32/33)
  - Frank, Marco (Box-folder 32/34)
  - Frankel, Cecil, Mrs. (Box-folder 32/35)
  - Frankenstein, Alfred and Sylvia, 1927-1932, undated (Box-folder 32/36)
  - Frankenstein, Alfred and Sylvia, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 32/37)
  - Frankenstein, Alfred and Sylvia, 1940-1946, undated (Box-folder 32/38)
  - Frankfurt am Main (Box-folder 32/39)
  - Franko, Sam (Box-folder 32/40)
  - Frauenheim, Norman (Box-folder 32/41)
  - Frazier, E. J. (Box-folder 32/42)
  - Frazier, Katharine (Box-folder 32/43)
  - Frederick, Kurt (Box-folder 32/44)
  - Frederick Stock Memorial Fund material (Box-folder 95/26)
  - Freeman, Henry and Florence (Box-folder 32/45)
  - Freeman, Jay Callender (Box-folder 32/46)
  - Freer, Eleanor Everest (Box-folder 32/47)
  - Freer Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C. see Guest, Grace Dunham
  - French, Daniel Chester (Box-folder 32/48)
  - Freund, Marya (Box-folder 32/49)
  - Frey, Willy (Box-folder 32/50)
  - "Fri" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Fricker, Herbert A. (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Friday Club see Chicago. Friday Club
  - Friday Morning Music Club (Washington, D.C.) see Washington, D.C. Friday Morning Music Club
  - Fried, Emma (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Friedberg, Annie, 1922-1934 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Friedberg, Annie, 1935 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - Friedberg, Annie, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Friedberg, Annie, 1940-1952, undated (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Friedlander, Ernst see also Pro Arte Quartet (Box-folder 33/8)
  - Friends of Albert Schweitzer see Schweitzer, Albert, friends of
  - Friends of Chamber Music (Box-folder 33/9)
  - Friends of Music at Stanford see Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford
  - Friends of Music (in the Library of Congress) see Library of Congress. Friends of Music
  - Frijsh, Povla (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Friskin, James and Kate see also Friskin, Rebecca Clarke (Box-folder 33/11)
  - Friskin, Rebecca Clarke, 1917-1929 (Box-folder 33/12)
  - Friskin, Rebecca Clarke, 1930-1943 (Box-folder 33/13)
  - Friskin, Rebecca Clarke, 1944-1953 (Box-folder 33/14)
  - Friskin, Rebecca Clarke, undated (Box-folder 33/15)
  - Fritsch, Antonia (Box-folder 33/16)
  - Fromm Foundation (Box-folder 33/17)
  - Frost, Frank J. (Box-folder 33/18)
  - Frysinger, Grace Elizabeth (Box-folder 33/19)
  - "Fu" miscellaneous see also "F" miscellaneous (Box-folder 33/20)
  - Fuchs, Emil (Box-folder 33/21)
  - Fuchs, Joseph and Lillian (Box-folder 33/22)
  - Fuerstner, Carl (Box-folder 33/23)
  - Fuld, James (Box-folder 33/24)
  - Fuleihan, Anis (Box-folder 33/25)
  - Fyffe, Elizabeth, 1917-1949 (Box-folder 33/26)
  - Fyffe, Elizabeth, 1950-1953, undated (Box-folder 33/27)
  - Fyffe, Elizabeth, undated (Box-folder 33/28)
  - "F" unidentified (Box-folder 33/29)
  - "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 33/30)
  - G. Ricordi & c. see Ricordi (Firm)
  - G. Schirmer, Inc. see Schirmer, G. (firm)
  - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip and Clara, 1917-1919, undated (Box-folder 33/31)
  - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip and Clara, 1920-1934, Also includes an undated Christmas card. (Box-folder 33/32)
  - Gabrilowitsch, Ossip and Clara, 1920 memorials (Box-folder 33/33)
  - Gade, F. Herman (Box-folder 33/34)
  - Gagnebin, Henri (Box-folder 33/35)
  - Galaxy Music Corp. (Box-folder 33/36)
  - Gale, Harlow (Box-folder 33/37)
  - Gale, Walter C. (Box-folder 33/38)
  - Gallaudet, Katharine F. (Box-folder 33/39)
  - Gallico, Paolo (Box-folder 33/40)
  - Gallo, Fortune (Box-folder 33/41)
  - Gange, Fraser (Box-folder 33/42)
  - Gannon, Theo F. see Columbia Broadcasting System. Gannon, Theo. F.
  - Gans, Issac (Box-folder 33/43)
  - Ganz, Rudolph (Box-folder 33/44)
  - "Gar" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 34/1)
  - Gardner, Samuel (Box-folder 34/2)
  - Garfield, H. W. see Williams College. Garfield, H. W.
  - Garland, Hamlin (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Garrett, Alice (Mrs. John) (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Gartz, Kate Crane see Crane-Gartz, Kate
  - Gasser, Robert L. (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Gassmann, Remi (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Gatherwright, Dorothy (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Gatti, Carlo (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Gatti, Guido M. (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Gatti-Casazza, Giulio (Box-folder 34/10)
  - Gauthier, Eva, 1922-1929 (Box-folder 34/11)
  - Gauthier, Eva, 1930-1937 (Box-folder 34/12)
  - Gauthier, Eva, undated (Box-folder 34/13)
  - Gauthier, Eva: carbons to Gauthier (Box-folder 34/14)
  - Gay, Maria (Box-folder 34/15)
  - "Ge" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 34/16)
  - Gebhard, Heinrich (Box-folder 34/17)
  - Geiringer, Karl (Box-folder 34/18)
  - Gelber, Ludwig (Box-folder 34/19)
  - Geneva (Box-folder 34/20)
  - Georgetown University (Box-folder 34/21)
  - Georgia. University (Box-folder 34/22)
  - Gerhardt, Elena (Box-folder 34/23)
  - Germany. Embassy, Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 34/24)
  - Gertler, André (Box-folder 34/25)
  - Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde in Wien see Vienna. Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde
  - "Gi" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 34/26)
  - Gibbon, Maud Winthrop (Box-folder 34/27)
  - Gibbons, John N. and Mrs. (Box-folder 34/28)
  - Gibbs, Becket (Box-folder 34/29)
  - Gibbs, W. S. see Fox Piano Company
  - Gieseking, Walter (Box-folder 34/30)
  - Gilbert, Clara C. (Box-folder 34/31)
  - Gilbert, Ella Lord (Box-folder 34/32)
  - Gilbert, Gertrude (Box-folder 34/33)
  - Gilbert, Giles (Box-folder 34/34)
  - Gilbert, Henry Franklin Belknap (Box-folder 34/35)
  - Gillen, Carrie R. (Box-folder 34/36)
  - Gillette, Florence (Box-folder 34/37)
  - Gilman, Lawrence (Box-folder 34/38)
  - Giorni, Aurelio (Box-folder 34/39)
  - Giuriati, Giovanni (Box-folder 34/40)
  - Giuseppe, [first name illegible] (Box-folder 34/41)
  - Gjerdrum, Henrik (Box-folder 34/42)
  - "Gl" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 34/43)
  - Glazer, David, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 34/44)
  - Glazer, David, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 34/45)
  - Glazer, David, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 34/46)
  - Glazer, David, undated (Box-folder 34/47)
  - Gluck, Alma (Box-folder 34/48)
  - "Go" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 34/49)
  - Godowsky, Leopold (Box-folder 34/50)
  - Goebel, Julius (Box-folder 34/51)
  - Goetschius, Percy (Box-folder 34/52)
  - Goetz, Margaret (Box-folder 34/53)
  - "Gol" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Golde, Walter (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Golden Gate International Exposition (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Goldman, Alfred R. (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Goldman, Edwin Franko (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Goldmark, Carl (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Goldmark, Rubin, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Goldmark, Rubin, 1920-1922 (Box-folder 35/8)
  - Goldmark, Rubin, 1923-1935 (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Goldmark, Rubin, undated (Box-folder 35/10)
  - Goldstein, Jerome (Box-folder 35/11)
  - Golestan, Stan (Box-folder 35/12)
  - Golia, Pasquale-Ciro (Box-folder 35/13)
  - Golschmann, Vladimir (Box-folder 35/14)
  - Good, Marian Bigler (Box-folder 35/15)
  - Goode, Blanche Piccoli (Box-folder 35/16)
  - Goodrich, Wallace see New England Conservatory
  - Goossens, Eugene (Box-folder 35/17)
  - Goossens, Leon (Box-folder 35/18)
  - Gordon, Jacques, 1920-1928 see also Gordon Musical Association and Gordon String Quartet (Box-folder 35/19)
  - Gordon, Jacques, 1929-1932 (Box-folder 35/20)
  - Gordon, Jacques, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 35/21)
  - Gordon, Jacques, 1939-1947 (Box-folder 35/22)
  - Gordon, Jacques, undated (Box-folder 35/23)
  - Gordon, Marie (Box-folder 35/24)
  - Gordon Musical Association (Box-folder 35/25)
  - Gordon String Quartet (Box-folder 35/26)
  - Gorton, Belle L. (Box-folder 35/27)
  - Goss, Madeleine B. (Box-folder 35/28)
  - Gottlieb, Victor and Eudice see also Shapiro, Eudice (Box-folder 35/29)
  - Gottschalk, Nathan (Box-folder 35/30)
  - Gould, Clara Hinton (Mrs. F.S.) (Box-folder 35/31)
  - Gow, George C. see Vassar College
  - Gowdy, Alma (dated material) (Box-folder 35/32)
  - Gowdy, Alma (undated material) (Box-folder 35/33)
  - "Gr" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Graham, Martha: correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Graham, Martha: correspondence, 1944 (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Graham, Martha: correspondence, 1945-1948, undated (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Graham, Martha: miscellaneous correspondence relating to the production of Appalachian Spring (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Graham, Martha: scenarios (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Graham, Martha: miscellaneous material relating to Appalachian Spring (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Graham, Martha: budgets (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Graham, Martha: publicity material (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Graham, Martha: clippings (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Grainger, Percy (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Grandjany, Marcel, 1930-1941 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Grandjany, Marcel, 1945-1951 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Grandjany, Marcel, undated (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Grant, Mazie H. (Box-folder 36/15)
  - Gratwick, Mitchell, Mrs. (Box-folder 36/16)
  - Graudan, Nikolai (Box-folder 36/17)
  - Graves, Merle D. (Box-folder 36/18)
  - Gray, Cecil (Box-folder 36/19)
  - Graz, Austria--Museums (Box-folder 36/20)
  - Grazer Urania (Box-folder 36/21)
  - Great Britain (Box-folder 36/22)
  - Greely, Philip (Box-folder 36/23)
  - Green, Margaret (Box-folder 36/24)
  - Green, Olive Mead (Mrs. Merrill H. Green) (Box-folder 36/25)
  - Green, Ray (Box-folder 36/26)
  - Greenbie, Marjorie (Box-folder 36/27)
  - Greene, Jerome D. see Harvard University. Greene, Jerome D.
  - Greenleaf, Sue (Box-folder 36/28)
  - Greenwich House (Box-folder 36/29)
  - Greenwood Music Camp (Box-folder 36/30)
  - Gregg, James E. see Hampton Institute
  - Gregg, Marjorie T. (Box-folder 36/31)
  - Gregor, Aelfrida M. (Box-folder 36/32)
  - Gregory, Addie Hubbard (Box-folder 36/33)
  - Greiner, A. W. see Steinway and Sons
  - Greville, Ursula (Box-folder 36/34)
  - Grey, Madeleine (Box-folder 36/35)
  - "Gri" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 36/36)
  - Griffes, Charles Tomlinson (Box-folder 36/37)
  - Griffis, Elliot (Box-folder 36/38)
  - Griller, Sidney (Box-folder 36/39)
  - Griller Quartet (Box-folder 36/40)
  - Grisez, Georges (Box-folder 36/41)
  - Groen, Niels (Box-folder 36/42)
  - Grote, Etta M. (Box-folder 36/43)
  - Grout, Donald Jay see Harvard University. Grout, Donald Jay
  - Grovlez, Gabriel (Box-folder 36/44)
  - Grümmer, Paul (Box-folder 36/45)
  - Gruenberg, Louis (Box-folder 36/46)
  - Grumman, Ellsworth (Box-folder 36/47)
  - Gruppo Universitario di Cultura Musicale, Milan see Milan. Gruppo Universitario di Cultura Musicale
  - "Gu" miscellaneous see also "G" miscellaneous (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Guest, Grace Dunham, 1924-1939 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Guest, Grace Dunham, 1940-1949 (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Guest, Grace Dunham, 1950 and undated (post-retirement) (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Guest, Grace Dunham, undated (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Guidi, Scipione (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Guilbert, Gilles (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Guild, Courtenay (Box-folder 37/9)
  - Guild for Musicians see Kahn, Erminie
  - Guilet Quartet (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Gunn, Glenn Dillard (Box-folder 37/11)
  - Gunston Hall (Box-folder 37/12)
  - Gustafson, Ester (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Gutberg, Ingrid and Karen (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Gutchë, Gene see Gutsche, Romeo
  - Gutman, Elizabeth (Box-folder 37/15)
  - Gutman, Ida (Box-folder 37/16)
  - Gutsche, Romeo (Box-folder 37/17)
  - Guttman, Louis (Box-folder 37/18)
  - Guzmán, Luis (Box-folder 37/19)
  - Gyring, Elizabeth (Box-folder 37/20)
  - "G" unidentified (Box-folder 37/21)
  - "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 37/22)
  - Habicht, Robert (Box-folder 37/23)
  - Haddock, G. Marston (Box-folder 37/24)
  - Hadley, Henry and Mrs. (Box-folder 37/25)
  - Hadow, W. Henry (Box-folder 37/26)
  - Haensel and Jones (Box-folder 37/27)
  - Hagedorn, Hermann (Box-folder 37/28)
  - Hageman, Richard (Box-folder 37/29)
  - Hager, Mina (Box-folder 37/30)
  - Hague, Eleanor (Box-folder 37/31)
  - Hahn, Reynaldo (Box-folder 37/32)
  - Haiss, D. (Box-folder 37/33)
  - "Hal" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 37/34)
  - Halász, László (Box-folder 37/35)
  - Hale, Philip and Irene (Box-folder 37/36)
  - Hale, Richard W. (attorney) (Box-folder 37/37)
  - Hale and Dorr, Attorneys see Library of Congress. Legal advice to E.S. Coolidge
  - Halleux, Laurent (Box-folder 37/38)
  - Halstead, Aline (Mrs. Albert) and Margaret (Box-folder 37/39)
  - Hamelin, Gaston (Box-folder 37/40)
  - Hamill, Charles H. (lawyer) (Box-folder 37/41)
  - Hamill, Ernest A. (Box-folder 37/42)
  - Hamilton, Clarence C. see Wellesley College. Hamilton, Clarence C.
  - Hamilton College (Box-folder 37/43)
  - Hamlin, Frank H. (Box-folder 37/44)
  - Hamlin, George (Box-folder 37/45)
  - Hammond, E. C. see Mount Holyoke College. Hammond, E. C.
  - Hammond, William Churchill (Box-folder 37/46)
  - Hampden, Walter (Box-folder 37/48)
  - Hampton Institute (Box-folder 37/47)
  - "Han" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 37/49)
  - Handel and Haydn Society (Boston, Mass.) (Box-folder 37/50)
  - Handley, A. H. (Box-folder 37/51)
  - Hanenfeldt, Mary M. (Box-folder 37/52)
  - Hanna, A. J. (Box-folder 37/53)
  - Hanson, Howard (Box-folder 37/54)
  - Harmati, Sandor and Ruth (Box-folder 37/55)
  - Harms, William (Box-folder 37/56)
  - Harnoncourt, Eberhard d' (Box-folder 37/57)
  - Harper's Bazaar (Box-folder 37/58)
  - "Harr" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Harris, George (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Harris, Leslie (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Harris, Roy, 1932 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Harris, Roy, 1933 (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Harris, Roy, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Harris, Roy, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Harris, Roy, 1940-circa 1950 (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Harris, Roy, undated (presumably pre-1937) (Box-folder 38/9)
  - Harris, Roy, undated (presumably 1937 or later) (Box-folder 38/10)
  - Harris, Roy, undated (Box-folder 38/11)
  - Harris, Wilhelmina (Box-folder 38/12)
  - Harris, William H. (Box-folder 38/13)
  - Harrison, Beatrice (Box-folder 38/14)
  - Harrison, Julius (Box-folder 38/15)
  - Harsányi, Tibor (Box-folder 38/16)
  - Hart House String Quartet (Box-folder 38/17)
  - Hartford Times (Box-folder 38/18)
  - Hartley, Walter E. see Occidental College. Miscellany
  - Hartley House Music School (Box-folder 38/19)
  - Hartmann, Arthur (Box-folder 38/20)
  - Hartt, Julius (Box-folder 38/21)
  - Harvard Glee Club (Box-folder 39/19)
  - Harvard Musical Association (Box-folder 39/22)
  - Harvard-Radcliffe Orchestra (Box-folder 39/20)
  - Harvard University see also Dumbarton Oaks, Hill, Edward Burlingame, Howe, Mark A. DeWolfe, Piston, Walter, Spalding, Walter R., Thompson, Randall
  - Harvard University. Board of Overseers (Box-folder 39/1)
  - Harvard University. Conant, James Bryant (Box-folder 39/2)
  - Harvard University. Davison, Archibald T. and Mrs., 1921-1936 (Box-folder 39/3)
  - Harvard University. Davison, Archibald T. and Mrs., 1937-1945 (Box-folder 39/4)
  - Harvard University. Dept. of Music. Miscellany (Box-folder 39/13)
  - Harvard University. Fogg Art Museum see also Forbes, Edward W. and Margaret (Box-folder 39/5)
  - Harvard University. Greene, Jerome D., 1935-1939 (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Harvard University. Greene, Jerome D., 1940-1944 (Box-folder 39/7)
  - Harvard University. Grout, Donald Jay (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Harvard University. Merritt, A. Tillman, 1936-1945 (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Harvard University. Merritt, A. Tillman, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Harvard University. Merritt, A. Tillman, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Harvard University. Merritt, A. Tillman, undated (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Harvard University. Miscellany (Box-folder 39/18)
  - Harvard University. President and Fellows of Harvard College. Miscellany (Box-folder 39/14)
  - Harvard University. Tercentenary Celebration (Box-folder 39/15)
  - Harvard University. Woodworth, G. Wallace (Box-folder 39/16)
  - Harvard University--various non-student institutions connected with the University (Box-folder 39/17)
  - Harvard University--various student institutions connected with the College and University (Box-folder 39/21)
  - Harwood, Edward C. (Box-folder 39/23)
  - Haubiel, Charles (Box-folder 39/24)
  - Haughton, Alison (Box-folder 39/25)
  - Hauser, Emil see Palestine Conservatory of Music
  - "Hav" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Haven, Minnie Speare (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Havre, Jean Baptiste and Mrs. (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Haweis, Margaret (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Hawkins, Erick (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Hawley, Annie Andros (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Hawley, Oscar H. (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Haydn Society (Boston, Mass.) (Box-folder 40/8)
  - Haydon, Glen see North Carolina University
  - Hayes, Helen (fund appeal) (Box-folder 40/9)
  - Hayes, Roland (Box-folder 40/10)
  - Haywood, Marjorie (Box-folder 40/11)
  - "He" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 40/12)
  - Hebert, Felix (Box-folder 40/13)
  - Hebrew University (Box-folder 40/14)
  - Hecht, Elias (Box-folder 40/15)
  - Heifetz, Benar and Olga (Box-folder 40/16)
  - Heifetz, Jascha (Box-folder 40/17)
  - Heinsheimer, Hans (Box-folder 40/18)
  - Hekking, Louis (Box-folder 40/19)
  - Helburn, Margaret (Box-folder 40/20)
  - Held, Conrad (Box-folder 40/21)
  - Helfer, Walter (Box-folder 40/22)
  - Henderson, Charles Belknap and Ethel (Box-folder 40/23)
  - Henderson, W. J. (Box-folder 40/24)
  - Hendricks, Ellwood (Box-folder 40/25)
  - Henri, Robert (Box-folder 40/26)
  - Henry, Harold (Box-folder 40/27)
  - Henry, Leigh, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 40/28)
  - Henry, Leigh, 1931 (Box-folder 40/29)
  - Henry, Leigh, 1932-1937 (Box-folder 40/30)
  - Henry, Leigh. Synopsis of lecture on Chamber Music & the Growth of Social Consciousness & Culture (Box-folder 40/31)
  - Henry, Stuart C. and Edith see Berkshire Museum
  - Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery see Huntington (Henry E.) Library and Art Gallery
  - Hentsch, Edith (Box-folder 40/32)
  - "Her" miscellaneous see also "H" miscellaneous (Box-folder 40/33)
  - Herbert, F. Hugh (Box-folder 40/34)
  - Herbert, Walter (Box-folder 40/35)
  - Herbert S. Stone & Company see Stone, Herbert S. & co.
  - Herleroy, Marguerite (Box-folder 40/36)
  - Herring, Hubert see Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America
  - Herrick, Myron T. (Box-folder 40/37)
  - Herter Norton, Mary Dows (Box-folder 40/38)
  - Hertz, Alfred (Box-folder 40/39)
  - Hertzka, Emil (Box-folder 40/40)
  - Herzog, Baron André (Box-folder 40/41)